Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trials, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
To complete the Elves reincarnation, Licht and his cohorts made their way to the Shadow Palace, which lies between this realm and the next.
At the conclusion of this process, any humans whose bodies had been possessed by the Elves would be sent to the Otherworld.
Don't screw this up, you hear me? I want you to surpass your damn limit!
Understood, sir!
Yami and Jack set off after Licht, while Asta and some of the other Black Bulls faced off with the Elven counterparts of Ghosh and his sister Marie.
Meanwhile, Vanessa, Magna, Charmy, Sally and Luck had been taken to Glamour World, where they fought a possessed Dorothy, captain of the Coral Peacocks and user of dream magic.
That's how it is. Everything that exists in Glamour World will eventually get drowsy.
Luckily, Dorothy's magic has the ability to make anything materialize, which Sally used to her advantage.
What this world needs most is an exit, exit, exit! Make one, please!
Aw, hell yeah!
But anyone who looks into Marie's eyes will be rendered unable to move, so Asta's team had a much more difficult fight on their hands.
Despite that, the Black Bulls pressed off.
I'm gonna stop you two no matter what! I will turn you back into the normal Ghosh and Marie!
I'll save my friend, I swear!
Since I know that Thorn's secret, it won't be hard to defeat it. It can't resist strong magic.
My sword's reacting to the magic!
Just keep flying around.
Careful, Oster!
Sorry!
Not
Let's
Tell me
朽ち果てた世界で
負けられぬ戦い達
びっくりするグラカペ
エヴァナナナ
負けるわけないじゃん
誰もらうと続く 省略 孝須 以上
Let us escape ourselves
We won't
Uh
haha
Why
So
You
Don't
Stop
All
全ての空のまでやるよ
ラッ!
ドリーン!
はやねっ!
ボルティマは金を作った...
ымやその書かことができるのが少し beiまれることを早めた!
平保にするのをバッスMaybeかすぎることが大きいことを人が suggestionと感じるし
No, we're trapped.
Man, we were so close!
You act like this is some kind of stupid game!
Damn it all!
Could've sworn we were home free!
I know, let's just wish for another exit!
Make us one more one!
I'd like to say it, Explosion Boy,
but if she's concentrating that hard on shutting them,
then we can make another one!
Oh, I got a delicious meal here,
so I just gotta eat my feelings!
That's your own cotton magic, moron!
Stay with us, Charmy!
If you fall asleep now, then you'll never wake up again!
Oh no, we'd better think of something quick,
or it's over for us.
It seems like anything goes in this crazy world.
Hey, I know!
If there aren't any rules in here,
then why don't we just make her fix this?
Huh? What's that mean?
We don't have time for any of your goofy ideas-
Just shut up for a second, okay?
Shut up!
Can I run something by you real quick, Sally?
First we're gonna...
And then...
I see!
That sounds like fun!
Yeah, it's definitely worth a try, at least.
Yes!
Hold it!
I need you to talk a lot louder!
This is exhausting!
If I say it louder, she'll hear me!
Okay, so do you have any brilliant ideas for making my plan work?
Of course I do!
I don't know what you're muttering about, but it's impossible for you to escape from this place.
You're doomed to sleep for all eternity.
Here goes!
You're the first one up to bat! Don't let us down!
I got no clue what's going on, but here goes!
Flame magic time bomb explosive scatter shot!
Trying to hide from me in my own domain?
Fools.
What's this?
Unlike the things your magic generates, the stuff that we create isn't real!
We made a doll from Charmy's cotton and Vanessa's thread!
Then we used Explosion Boy's flame magic to produce a heat mirage and blurring!
Which resulted in a fairly convincing replica!
For a moment...
You thought it might be real!
Just like we wanted you two!
When I was being controlled, there were two connected spirits inside my body.
Me, and the elf who was possessing me.
I bet that doll makes you think of her, whether you want to or not!
How dare you...
The real Dorothy Unsworth is still in there!
There she is!
The captain of the coral peacocks makes her comeback!
She's just the person we need!
She's taking a nap!
Huh?
Oh, that's right.
She's a famously frequent sleeper.
Crap, don't tell me she's already fell into that eternal slumber thing!
She woke up!
Quit goofing off and get us out of here, would ya?
I can barely keep my eyes open!
I take it you're the ones who summoned me here?
If so...
That's fantastic!
Good job putting that plan together, everybody!
Now leave the rest to me!
After all, I'm a captain!
You're so chipper!
I have to ask, how old are you?
You look so young for a captain!
I mean, I'm curious too, but I think that could wait.
I'm 27 years old!
I know, I look incredible for my age, right?
That's fair!
That's my thing!
She's even older than I am!
That's enough.
Sleep within my soul once more.
But both of us have finally found somebody we can share our dreams with!
We should have some fun!
I don't play with humans!
Take that!
Whoa!
That's crazy!
Wow!
The dream world is really interesting!
I want to study it more!
That sure looks yummy!
Amazing!
She's strong enough to challenge her own elf form!
Let's replenish our mana!
Hey!
Wanna cook?
Always!
Now we can escape for sure!
Be back soon everyone!
I can't get close enough to him!
This sucks!
Want to live?
You better close your eyes!
How am I supposed to-
Surrender, brat!
Arrrgh!
Thanks for catching me!
We're transferring a bit of our mana to Henry.
Marvin is it! He's absorbing our power faster than normal!
Get inside! Hurry!
I'm doing my best!
At this point, I can only use my dark form about two and a half more times.
And I used it once before I got here, so it won't work for long.
I hope this works! Transformation magic! Magic conversion!
There is a mini black ball!
Here we go!
Sorry, that's not good enough.
You didn't mirror the parts that are expelling the magic.
I'm in range.
This is where we say goodbye.
Wait, what's Henry doing?
You're killing yourself?
And you plan to take me down with you?
Not quite.
This will only kill me.
Protecting my friends is the one reason I've survived till now.
What is this?
My mana's draining.
Outside the hideout, I absorb magic at a much higher rate.
And this isn't a spell, so her ability can't cancel it out.
It's no use, human.
My power is immense.
I've got more than enough to spare.
So you'll die for nothing.
Fine by me.
My job is done anyway.
I'm just happy I could fight with my friends.
I'm sure they'll find some way to stop you once I'm gone.
Now.
It's your turn.
You're not even close to John, Henry.
Don't die.
Hi, Henry.
You're the guy with that illness that sucks up magic, right?
I'm Asta, the newest member of the Black Bulls.
The captain told me about this place after I found it by accident.
But I don't have magic, so don't you worry.
You're embarrassed to meet them because you always take their mana?
It's fine.
Seriously, nobody's going to get upset at you for that.
This team is full of weirdos.
We've all got our own quirks, so you'll fit right in here.
Maybe once I get a good handle on my magic absorption.
Okay.
One day, I'll say hi to my squad.
Sounds good, buddy.
We'll be waiting for you.
It'll be even more fun once you meet the squad in person.
It's like a dream.
Before I met them, I was all by myself.
I didn't care how long I'd live.
But now...
I don't want to die.
I want to live on with my friends.
Please don't go.
We'll miss you.
Poison magic, we're good through.
Poison magic, we're good with the THIS SPADES.
Poison magic, we're good through this past me.
Poison magic, we're good through this past гар voy.
Between the HE
That's enough.
Give those bodies back to Goshen Marie right now.
They're our friends.
We won't let them disappear.
Damned humans.
I can't use my magic.
Our power has been disabled.
They put up a barrier.
We're trapped.
No, my spell.
I can't get it to work.
This goes against the laws of nature.
Why?
Is it because of a human magic item?
That's...
Excellent.
I'm bursting with power.
Now, elven magic is ours to do with as we please.
The princess is useless.
She's carrying the child of an elf.
She's not fit to be a royal now.
Only the human race should possess strong magic like this.
Just the idea of coexisting with these creatures is disgusting.
We'll make them pay dearly for leading one of our own astray.
From this moment forward, this land will be governed by human royalty.
I'll never forget those vile human faces, even in death.
So eager to spill our elven blood.
They slaughtered our kind out of pure greed.
And then their rotten minds twisted the truth beyond recognition, allowing them to be angry at us.
I still hear their repulsive laughter.
I will never understand such senseless violence.
What they did to us was sick and unforgivable.
My rage will not be satisfied until every last one of them is torn to shreds.
I curse the human race!
But these humans, they aren't like them.
They're fighting for their friends, the same as my people fought for each other.
I'm sorry.
At this rate, my malice will take over completely and I won't be myself at all anymore.
Do as you will.
Please forgive me, Eklat.
Brother, I love you.
I want you to stay by my side forever.
I have no choice.
I need my friends back.
That sword, it even erases the forbidden magic.
Licht, why did you?
Oh well.
I know Patry and Raya worked hard, but I'm afraid I have to let you all down.
This is where it ends for me.
We never should have used that forbidden spell.
A power that could make it so something never happened.
Do you think that exists?
For every action taken in this life, there must always be consequences.
You should do your best to remember that.
Human.
I know.
I'll never forget you two.
Goodbye.
You couldn't be more right.
There isn't a single human you can trust.
No matter how close you get, they're still strangers.
Everyone puts themselves first and tries to make their own life easier.
They'll betray you without a moment's hesitation.
I'm no different.
As long as Marie and I were happy, that was all that mattered.
That was enough for me.
Oh gosh.
Come on, friend.
Please wake up.
Rise and shine.
Goosh.
Excuse me, I'm glad you're back to normal and everything, but you didn't have to whack me on the forehead like that.
Please respect my personal space.
Are you all right?
Marie?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm so happy I didn't hurt you.
We're fine.
It's good to see that you're not hurt either.
You're all such idiots.
As long as you're safe, that's what counts.
You almost died for someone else.
And now, our hideout is destroyed too.
I only think about Marie and myself.
Our safety is my one priority.
That's the only reason I chose to join the Black Bulls.
I never planned on becoming friends with any of you losers.
In fact, if I'm being honest, I've never trusted anyone in this group at all.
Don't say that.
Look, the point is, you guys shouldn't have saved me.
He really doesn't get it, does he?
I thought he was smarter than that.
I mean, we already knew he only cared about himself and his sister, so...
You're stupid.
It's not what you're supposed to say right now.
Come on!
Look at your friends!
Please don't be mad.
Ah, damn it.
Thanks for saving us, bunch of jerks.
You're a jerk and you're creepy, so there!
Get off me or else...
You know you love us, you creepy jerk.
Stop calling me the same two things!
This is awkward!
Then leave me alone!
Gordon and Ghost, best of friends.
Yeah, I don't think so.
Ah!
Come on, really?
How good I hate this fight!
It's getting so interesting!
Interesting!
Be quiet!
At this point, nothing really surprises me anymore.
Thank goodness for that kitty cat.
We'd be toast without her.
Heads up.
Huh?
I didn't realize my glamour world couldn't withstand the dreams of two people.
It's collapsing.
Woo!
That was a blast!
I feel much better.
Take care of my body, okay?
See you never!
I'm glad I got to meet you.
You have to see now.
Not all humans are consumed by greed and betrayal.
These kids are more than enough proof of that.
Our enemy's really powerful.
So we can go all out, right?
Yeah, sounds good to me.
Her power and magic were top-notch, but it didn't do her much good against our spells.
She should have finished us off in one blow instead of giving us a chance to come up with a strategy.
That's what happens when we all work together.
That's true.
Combo spell!
Flame lightning exploding cannon!
What's going on?
Oh, great!
It looks like everybody made it!
Good to see ya!
Oh, Ghosh.
I'm so happy you're back to your old self.
Now we can all be best friends again.
You need a snack!
Don't go cramming food in my mouth, short stuff!
It is pretty tasty, though.
It's an extra special treat that restores your mana.
You eat up too, kiddo!
Wow, this is so delicious!
I don't know what you're doing here, Psycho, but stay away from my sister, got it?
Aw, just one experiment.
I'll kill you!
Hey, wait, we didn't get to fight each other.
We should do that right now!
No way!
Looks like the captain of the coral peacocks is back!
Back to sleep, you mean?
Damn, I can't believe we missed the whole thing.
Yeah, guess so.
Oh no, I slipped!
Why is everybody falling from the sky?
Somebody want to fill me in here?
Um, oh, hey guys!
I just fell off that broom up there on accident.
It's not like I wanted to join you all.
Don't ask, princess!
Now get your damn foot off me!
I'm royalty.
I'm allowed to step on you.
Not fair!
Hey, Charmy!
Go feed Henry some of that magic grub!
Right!
I bet he's super hungry by now!
I'm famished.
All right!
Finral's the only one we're missing.
The rest of the Black Bulls are back together!
Once we recharge, we'll go help the captain!
Yeah!
We'll be right back!
called the Glamour World!
And to show my thanks, I'll grant a wish for each of you!
Ah!
I want some delicious meat to chow down on, pretty please!
Say no more!
Here you go!
Oh, jeez!
I want to fight someone to my heart's content!
Sure thing!
With these on, you can hit people all day long without hurting them!
With all this combat going on, I could use a few good skincare products!
And I want to be totally buff and chiseled like Captain Yami is!
Snow's mad!
Snow's proud, you two!
Hey!
Why can't I feel my face?
Oh no!
This is the disaster!
We're off to the Shadow Palace! It's time to end this! And then the whole squad will be back together!
Black Clover, page 113, Storming the Shadow Palace!
My magic is never giving up!